Preliminary Inventory of the James Hayes papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- IX. Lease contract (Box 52)
  - 2. Lease of land (Box 52)
    - Li Tong (Folder 52: 14)
    - Liang Geng (Folder 52: 15)
    - Huo Jing, Huo Xueqiang (Folder 52: 16)
  - 3. Lease of shop (Box 52)
    - Huang Wuzi, big house (Folder 52: 17)
    - Ni Nongguan (Folder 52: 18)
    - Huang Xiufu (Folder 52: 19)
- X. Contract stub (Box 52-53)
  Arranged by household
  - Liang Caijie (Folder 53: 1)
  - Yan Shengcong (Folder 53: 2)
  - Liao Ruyu (Folder 53: 3)
  - Lai Jingmao (Folder 53: 4)
  - Zheng Jicheng (Folder 53: 5)
  - Ruan Jianqian (Folder 53: 6)
  - Yang Yuepin (Folder 53: 7)
  - Huang Huanzhao (Folder 53: 8)
  - Yang Binxing (Folder 53: 9)
  - Yu Guzu (Folder 53: 10)
  - Chen Qin (Folder 53: 11)
  - Chen Yili (Folder 53: 12)
  - Chen Derun (Folder 53: 13)
  - Chen Beiyuan (Folder 53: 14)
  - Chen Yingxiang (Folder 53: 15)
  - Li Dunzheng (Folder 53: 16)
  - Yang Tianshu (Folder 53: 17)
  - Yang Taichao (Folder 53: 18)
  - He Xiufeng (Folder 53: 19)
  - Yihe Tang (Folder 53: 20)
  - Cai-Lin (Folder 53: 21)
  - He Yunfang's wife - Li (Folder 53: 22)
  - Li Yuquan (Folder 53: 23)
  - He Xiufeng (Folder 53: 24)
  - Zhang Xianghe (Folder 53: 25)
  - He Xiufeng (Folder 53: 26)
  - Li Chongli (Folder 53: 27)
  - Chen Derun (Folder 53: 28)
  - He Xiufeng (Folder 53: 29)
  - Lian Fanyu (Folder 53: 30)
  - Li Chongli (Folder 53: 31)
  - Wu Xueguang (Folder 53: 32)
  - Zhan Zhehi (Folder 53: 33)
  - Feng Shengfeng (Folder 53: 34)
  - Huang Yashi (Folder 53: 35)
  - Liu Canxing (Folder 53: 36)
  - Yang Guozhi (Folder 53: 37)
  - Yang Jiyi (Folder 53: 38)
  - Zhang Jianze (Folder 53: 39)
- Oversize scroll (On shelf)
- Incremental Materials (Box 54-55)
  - Tian'ran Tang traditional Chinese medicine, receipts, prices, and accounts, undated (Box-folder 54: 1)
  - Personal correspondence, undated (Box-folder 54: 2-3)
  - Railway department and financial department public bonds, 1926-1930 (Box-folder 54: 4)
  - Seals of the Zengcheng government from 1947 and a military training certificate from 1942 (Box-folder 54: 5)
  - Civil servant punishment law, tax sheet, correspondence, and reports, 1932-1947 (Box-folder 54: 6)
  - Siam (Thailand) Overseas Chinese donation to Zengcheng, 1947-1947 (Box-folder 54: 7)
  - Charges of corruption against the head of Zengcheng county, Mo Yao Kun, 11 May 1947 (Box-folder 54: 8)
  - Written judgement of Taishan county on the Weng case, 1925 (Box-folder 54: 9, Box-folder 55: 1)
  - Weng people of the Taishan County, Guangdong materials, 1925 (Box-folder 55: 2)
    Includes donations for building a school, petitions, drafts, and other materials.
  - Royal Hong Kong Jockey Club menu for the Queen and Duke of Edinburgh, 22 October 1986 (Box-folder 55: 3)
  - Local traditional Chinese wedding brochure, 1986-1987 (Box 55: 3)
  - "The War, the Japanese Occupation, and Tsuen Wan," by James Hayes (Box-folder 55: 4)
  - "Japanese Occupation of Hong Kong 1941-1945", undated (Box-folder 55: 5-7)
    Also inlcudes other papers on historic topics.